<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[We On Bikes Blog RSS Feed]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bicycle touring is our passion; practical tips, cycling routes, packing lists - we share our experiences on bikepacking, bike trips and cycling life with you in our blog and book.]]></description><link>https://weonbikes.com/en/</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 11:07:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[13 Spectacular Cycling Highlights in Norway]]></title><description><![CDATA[All cycling routes in Norway are beautiful. But which are the ones not to miss? And on which long-distance cycling routes are the highlights? The most spectacular cycling routes with interactive map and GPS routes to download.]]></description><link>https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/cycling-routes-norway-3/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/cycling-routes-norway-3/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trolls, Fjords, Midnight Sun - Norway by bicycle]]></title><description><![CDATA[Midnight sun, fjord views, carefree cycling into the evening? This is a bikepacking summer in Norway. Read here which long-distance cycle routes are signposted through Norway's breathtaking landscapes. With GPX routes to download.]]></description><link>https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/cycling-routes-norway-2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/cycling-routes-norway-2/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cycle Touring in Norway: Routes and Planning]]></title><description><![CDATA[Summer cycling holidays in Norway? This is possible with good preparation. Read what you have to consider when cycling in Norway and which signposted long-distance routes lead through the breathtaking landscapes of this Arctic country: North Cape, Lofoten, Geiranger, Hardangervidda, Fjord Norway. With GPX routes to download.]]></description><link>https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/cycling-routes-norway-1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/cycling-routes-norway-1/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Solo on the Camino de Santiago Part 4: Luck in Misfortune]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bicycle trip solo on the Way of St. James from the Netherlands to Santiago de Compostela and back. 4620 km of cycling without a tent; Camera and wallet stolen, but with a flower on the handlebars. Part 4: How there is always a way thanks to helpful people everywhere. Day 25 to 27 from my travel diary ...]]></description><link>https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/camino-santiago-by-bicycle-part-4/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/camino-santiago-by-bicycle-part-4/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Solo by Bike to Santiago de Compostela Part 3: theft]]></title><description><![CDATA[By bike solo on the Way of St. James from the Netherlands to Santiago de Compostela and back. 4620 km without a tent with little money. Part 3: Theft! What will my Camino be like without camera and wallet? Read day 22 to 24 of my travel diary... ]]></description><link>https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/camino-santiago-by-bicycle-part-3/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/camino-santiago-by-bicycle-part-3/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Solo by Bike to Santiago de Compostela Part 2: Col du Somport]]></title><description><![CDATA[By bike solo on the Way of St. James from the Netherlands to Santiago de Compostela and back. 4620 km without a tent with little money. Part 2: over the Pyrenees. Col du Somport and 7 other Pyrenees passes for cycling pilgrims. With routes to download.]]></description><link>https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/camino-santiago-by-bicycle-part2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/camino-santiago-by-bicycle-part2/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Solo by Bike to Santiago de Compostela Part 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[Solo cycling tour on the Way of St. James from the Netherlands to Santiago de Compostela and back. 4620 km without a tent on a micro budget, but with a flower on the handlebars: 10 days in the company of Jaqueline, my travel campanula]]></description><link>https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/camino-santiago-by-bicycle-part-1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/camino-santiago-by-bicycle-part-1/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lisbon Tagus Bay by Bicycle: a Pizza Quest]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bike tour to our neighbor's pizzeria! 5 km as the crow flies become 25 km by bike around two side arms of the Tagus Bay. Read here what it's like to cycle on the south banks of Lisbon.]]></description><link>https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/lisbon-tagus-bay-pizzeria-by-bicycle/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/lisbon-tagus-bay-pizzeria-by-bicycle/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[By bicycle around 3 Seas in Europe]]></title><description><![CDATA[Around the Baltic Sea, North Sea and Mediterranean Sea by bicycle? In this article you'll find cycling routes for such adventures. With GPX for download.]]></description><link>https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/3-european-seas-by-bike/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/3-european-seas-by-bike/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Find the right saddle in 7 steps]]></title><description><![CDATA[Find the saddle that matches your anatomy in 7 steps. Learn which specs are important. Width, form, material, grooves and cut-out - find out which bike saddle is the right one for you and your cycling style.]]></description><link>https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/how-to-choose-your-saddle/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/how-to-choose-your-saddle/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to adjust a Shimano Nexus 8 Gear Shifter]]></title><description><![CDATA[In this article you'll learn how to adjust the Shimano Nexus 8 gear hub in 3 easy steps. With video. No tools required. Why is this even important: The Shimano Nexus 8 is a great gear shifter – but only if it is precisely adjusted.]]></description><link>https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/adjust-shimano-nexus-8-gear-shifter/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/adjust-shimano-nexus-8-gear-shifter/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Commuting by bicycle – Start easy and safe]]></title><description><![CDATA[Learn a safe and easy start to commuting by bicycle through the city. Save time and money and improve your fitness while getting to work on your bicycle.]]></description><link>https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/commuting-by-bicycle-for-starters/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/commuting-by-bicycle-for-starters/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[7 Popular Bicycle Routes in Europe for Summer Holidays]]></title><description><![CDATA[For bike touring in your summer holiday the route options in Europe are endless. Learn about 7 insanely popular routes with gpx downloads to get to know country and people while relaxing on your ride.]]></description><link>https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/7-cycling-routes-for-bike-tour-holidays/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/7-cycling-routes-for-bike-tour-holidays/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[3 steps to measure your sit bone distance]]></title><description><![CDATA[Here is how to measure the distance between your sit bones in 3 easy steps by yourself. The sit bone distance is an important measurement to calculate your optimum saddle width, because to be comfortable on your bike for hours in row you will need a saddle that fits your anatomy.]]></description><link>https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/measuring-sitbone-width-3-steps/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/measuring-sitbone-width-3-steps/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[7 cycling routes through Europe North to South]]></title><description><![CDATA[Seven most popular long-distance cycling routes in Europe for bike touring from North to South with GPX and KML download. Read all about Europe's vast cycling route network. Part 1 is about EuroVelo 1, 3, 7, 8, 11, 13 and the Europe Divide Trail. Is one of them a candidate for our cape-to-cape tour?]]></description><link>https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/7-cycling-routes-europe-north-to-south/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/7-cycling-routes-europe-north-to-south/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[She by bicycle - every day is Women's Day]]></title><description><![CDATA[Cycling for women: Does the ladies' bike exist? What does women have to consider when choosing a saddle and how does she ride a bike during menstruation? Bicycle frames, underpants and women's mobility are the topics of our blog post on Women's Day.]]></description><link>https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/she-by-bicycle/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/she-by-bicycle/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bicycle touring blog and events 2022]]></title><description><![CDATA[WeOnBikes first blog post. Here you'll find out about our next bike touring topics, which cycling events you can visit live again in 2022 and which ones regularly, and what we are planning with our website and our book From Moscow to the North Cape by bicycle.]]></description><link>https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/bicycle-touring-blog-and-events-2022-posts-and-plans-on-weonbikes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://weonbikes.com/en/blog/bicycle-touring-blog-and-events-2022-posts-and-plans-on-weonbikes/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>